<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on BluestNight</title>
    <link>https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on BluestNight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 10:26:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Events: Overhauled</title>
      <link>https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/events-overhauled/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 10:26:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/events-overhauled/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Time for another big update to BluestNight! In this episode, the events system has been overhauled to look nicer and provide more functionality than previously. Also, a some other semantic changes to watch out for while updating.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Privacy Policies And Optimizations</title>
      <link>https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/easy-privacy-policy-optimizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 10:26:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/easy-privacy-policy-optimizations/</guid>
      <description>Iubenda: Easy Privacy Policies BluestNight now comes with support for privacy policies generated by Iubenda (referral link). Iubenda is a simple solution for owners of websites that require a privacy policy (i.e. collect any sort of data from their users). Policies are assembled by choosing data-collecting services from a large list, customizing them as necessary, and clicking &amp;ldquo;Save.&amp;rdquo;
  The service selection dialog of Iubenda.   Free Accounts Free accounts are limited to a single privacy policy and may only include the policy on the site in the form of a button that opens a dialog box on the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BluestNight is All Grown Up!</title>
      <link>https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/all-grown-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 10:26:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluestnight.shadow53.com/posts/all-grown-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On March 20th, 2017, I made the first commit in the BluestNight repository. Back then, BluestNight was little more than my attempt to create a cleaner-written version of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/mainroad&#34;&gt;Mainroad&lt;/a&gt; theme after I grew frustrated with maintaining the fork I made, named &amp;ldquo;Darkroad&amp;rdquo; (it was a dark version of Mainroad).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
